Inventory of the Gordon Leo McDonough papers 0366
USC Libraries Special Collections
- File of BILLS/RELIEF bills sponsored/introduced by Sen. McDonough
  - BILLS introduced/sponsored by Sen McDonough 83 Congress, 1953/54
    - Board of Harbor Commissioners
    - Annual Reports Nr 45
    - Annual Reports, 1951
    - Master File McDonough 83 Congress
    - Private Relief Bills Introced 83 COngress (listing), 1953-54
    - Not re-introduced Bills
      - formerly HR 316 Federal Saving loan Amendment Bill H R 7699 RR 316, 1953, '52 '54; 6017
      - allowance for members of houseof Representatives for postage..., 1954; 7313
      - L A national cemetary, 1954; 8438
      - Protect U S fisherman in lawfull operstion on high seas.., 1954; 9285
  - RELIEF BILLS (same arr.)
    - Aiko Kinjo H R 843 854 674, 1953, '52; H R 843 (Box Box 8)
    - Roman Bugoslaw Massalski H R 941 6449 HJRES 476 Private Bill 5756, 1953 '52 '54; 844
    - Sella Rebner H R 848 Private Law 483, 1953,'52 '54; 849
    - Hugh L Mann H R 5616, 1953, '51 '52; 852
    - Wai-Jan Low Fong, 1954; 1171
    - Constantin David, Paul Davis Etc. 51 H R 1260 4511 6370, 1953,'49 '50 '; 1350
    - Friedberg H R 849, 1953, '52 '54; 4015
    - Shoze ohsuga, 1953 '54; 5166
    - David J Daze, 1953, '51; 5461
    - Fong Way Chong H R 5125, 1953,' '51 '54; 6497
    - Sun Yue Hien (chu Tseung), 1953, '53; 7360
    - Suszko, 1954; 8612
    - Milton Relief McCarthy, 1954
  - File of RELIEF BILLS 84 Congress sponsored/intr. by Sen McDonogh, 1955
    - Li Chiw Fu H R 4014 4705 5116 6449 Private Law 14, 1955, '53 '54; H R 1196 (Box Box 9)
    - Kenneth Lau H R 4501 Private Law 513, 1955, '54; 1198
    - Kaida, 1955; 1199
    - Dervan, 1955, '54; 1201
    - Merritt H R 8742 Private Law 138, 1955, '54; 1202
    - Lomm (Johnson) H R 1201 5488[UNK] Private Law 15, 1954, '55; 1203
    - Sobrali, 1955, '54; 1204
    - Jacob H R 3753 Private Law 159, 1955, '53 '54; 1205
    - Szekeres H R 7098, 1955, '53 '52; 1206
    - Isaac Piha H R 7939, 1955, '54; 1211
    - Akune H R 854 Public Law 515, 1955, '53 '52; 1212
    - David H R 1350 Private Law 583, 1956, '55; 3857
    - Ho family (Chai Wook Sook Yung, 1955, '56; 4499
    - Granados, 1955, '56; 4502
    - Lubke H R 1173 5620 5681, 1955; 5679
    - Young H R 5679 Public Law 414, 1955; 5680
    - Ralph Chen H R 10208, 1955, '54; 6792
  - RELIEF BILLS
    - Nigolian H R 7358, 1955 '54; 1195 (Box Box 9)
    - Graves, 1955; 1197
    - Howe 19 H R 1200 4502 4499 6792 10209, 1955 '54; 1200
    - Ajderian H R 4705 3857 H Con Res 89, 1955, '53 '56 '57; 1207
    - Estjer Moreno H R 9828 Private Law 514, 1955, '54 '56; 1208
    - Numeriano Lay May H R 4649 Private Law 546, 1956, '53 '55; 1209
    - Hechanova H R 8201, 1956; 1577
    - Vahl H R 5024, 1955, '56; 4501
    - Stahl H r 851 7306, 1955, '51 '52 '53 '54; 5389
    - Cheng, 1955, '57 '58; 5681
    - Shimizoo Noriko H J Res 638 Private Law 809, 1955, '56; 6192
    - Stammreich Private Law 371, 1956 '57 '55; 7167
    - Kelly, 1955, '56; 7168
    - Vonka, R (46, 1955 '54; 7654
    - King Man Huang, 1955, '56; 8055
    - Glen McAllister, 1955, '54 '52; 8144
    - Mc Donough Treaty Amendment H J Res 57 69 325, 1955 '54 '51; H J RES 59
    - Treaty Amend. (Bar ass. Bill), 1954 '55; 99
    - Treaty Amendment (Bricker) H J Res 59 99, 1955 '56; 60
    - Directory, 1955
    - Report 1st Session 84 Congress
  - Bills sponsored/introduced by Sen. McDonough, 1956/63
    Arranged by Bills in folios
    - Status of Forces Agreement Repeal, 1961; H.J. RES 49 (Box Box 10)
    - Treaty Amendment, 1961; 50
    - Proclaim National Teachers Day, 1961; 51
    - Equal Rights Amendment, 1961; 52
    - Establish National Teachers Day, 1961, '53 '61 '62; 53
    - Equal Rights H.J.Res 62, 1956, '57 '58 '59 '57; 92
    - Joint Garage Bomb Shelter, 1951, '49 '50 '51 '52; 93
    - Community Health Week H.J. RES 604, 1962, '61 '62; 204/566
    - Inauguration Day as a Holiday, 1961; 366
    - Delaware- New yersey Compact, 1961, '62; 555
    - Communistic Arms Contraband, 1962; 622
    - State of Fonflict, 1962; 623
    - Aquisition of Sites for Federal Buildins outside D of C, 1951, '49; H.R. 1365 9525
    - Mass Transportation H.R.8598, 1962 '61
    - Teacher Remembrance Day, 1961; H.T.RESS 339
    - Baltic States, 1962; H.CON. RES 444
    - Captive Nations Week, 1962; H.Res 555
    - Communist Legislation Bills not for re-introduction McDonough Private Bills (numerical listing), 1962; H.G. Res 623
    - Flag display H.Res 48, 1961, '50 '51 '57; H Res. 41
      General note
      FILE of remarks made by Sen. McDonough
      in original sequence
      no letter contents
  - BILLS introduced by Sen.McDonough, 1957-1960
    Arranged by Bill #.
    - Award to Purple Heart Veterans H R 330 332 5514 5667 10390 1172 R L 661, 1957, '56; H R 330 (Box Box 11)
    - Prisoner of War Compensation, 1957; 1172
    - Increase in civil service retirement benefits 1957 H R 3792 7562, 1173
    - Repeal Motion picture admission tax H R 157 167 1586, 1957 '53; 1177
    - Protection for banks, saving loan association from circulation of false rumour, 1957 '53; 1179
    - Extension remodelling terminal annex Post Office H R 332 5014 P L 519, 1957'55; 1181
    - Compensation to employers f. collecting witholding tax H R321 1352 5320 S 1008, 1957; 1188
    - Certain awards ofcombat infantry badge H R 554 H J RES 59 60 99, 1958, '55 '57; 1189
    - To increase pensions for civil service employees, 1957; 1193
    - For Federal polisy to take Gov't out of compettion with Private Enterprises H R 4797 4887 11094, 1955 '58; 1294
    - Smog Bill H R 2347 3183 3730 4466 7476 S 411, 1957; 1297
    - Tipp Bills H R 1290 2778 2779 13625 13626, 1959, '58; 2489
    - Extend duration of Federal Airpollution Control Law, 1959; 3183
    - Equalize pay retired member uniformed services H R 2879, 3328
    - Reinmbursement of State Local Property Taxes H R3592 3603, 1959; 3600
    - Amend Internal Revenue Code to assist Small independant businesses, 1954 1959; 3908
    - Weather modification Colorado River S 943, 1959; 4200
    - Weather modification, 1959; 4209
    - Amend title 11 of Social Security Act, 1959, '60; 4505
    - Repeal Federal Transportion Telephone Tax, 1959; 4512
    - Housing Bonds (Amend section 103 of 1 R Code '54), 1959; 5096
    - Housing Bill, 1959; 8188
    - Health benefits retired Federal employee's S 2575, 1959, '60; 8836
    - Bridge Canyon Project, 1960; 10617
    - Amend Title 1 of National Housing Act, 1960; 12127
    - Funds for Public Facilities Loans, 1960; 12173
    - Funds for purchases of mortgeges -housing, 12174
    - Amend title VII of National Housing Act, 1960; 12213
    - Remove limitation on certain aggregate amount of outstanding mortgage insurance, 1959, '60; 12214
    - Simpson-Dorn-Davis-Bailey H R 12591 11250, 12511
    - National Teachers Day, 1959; H J RES 91
    - Status of Armedn Forces H R 334 H J RES 61,309, 1959, '55 '56 '57; 93
    - L A World Fair H J RES 144, 1959; 462
  - BILLS introducd/sponsored by San.McDonough, 1957-1960
    Arr. by Bill nr.
    Horizontal arr l: Bill nr., year(s) of introduction relative correspondance, related Bills
    - Construction L A Customs House 84thCongr 1St Session 1955, H R 139 138 1367 1362 1361 2655 4506, H R 330 (Box Box 12)
    - RELIEF Nicholas Katem H R 4422 Private Law 491, 1953, '54; 848
    - L A Postoffice Expension H R 331 1184 1363 1555 5013, 1957; 861
    - Increase Pension widows Spanish-Amercan War Veterans 85 Congress 1 Session '57 H R 358 2867, 1957 '54 '56 '58; 1190 4684
    - Relief Masireuieh H R 6295, 1954, '55; 1213
    - King Kay Kwong 85 Congr. H R 1579 10094, 1956, '57; 1579
    - Construction L A Customs House 85th Congress 1 Sesson, 1957, '48 '53 '55 '56 '57; 4682
    - Campbell Plan H R 330 4929 2655 Public Law 519, '56
    - Raise Public Debt, 1957, '53; 6627
    - Hoover Commission S 434, 1958, '57; 8002
    - National Teachers Day thr '57, '59 H R 330 3676 H J RES 57 58 60 61 91 467, 1960, '52; H JES 90
    - Treaties International Agreements H J RES 4 S 694 U S Offivce Memo: Communism, 1959; 94
    - Folders of following files
    - California Republican Deligation, 1958/ 1957
    - Candidate for Minority Clerk (Roberts)
    - Copies of BILLs 82 Congress 1 Session (Non Sorted), 1951
    - Copies of BILLs 82 2 Session (Non Sorted), 1951
    - Copies of BILLs 84 1 Session (Non Sorted), 1955
    - Federal Office Building in Civic Center, 1947
    - McDonough Complememtary letters, 1978 '58
    - Stationary Room House of Representatives, 1957
    - For Construction L A Customs HOuse Fedxral Office Building H R 4682 Public Law 519, 1955, '56; H R 4929
  - Relief Bills in folders with separators Arr. by bill nrs. Hor. name, year(s) of introduction correspondance, related bill, 1957/62
    - Baladi HR 12156, 1962 '60 '61; H. R. 2363 (Box Box 13)
    - Delos Santos, 1961; 2661
    - Visuch HR 2689 Public Law 568, 1957 '58; 2689
    - Nappert (not introduced), 1957 '58; 2690
    - Adams, 1961 '60; 2994
    - Sharp HR 2082 2381, 1961 '62 '57; 3395
    - Serayoarian HR 1563 1564 7923 7924, 1962 '57 '59; 4029
    - Sweeny HR 11556, 1962 '60; 4197
    - Jamilosaa HR 4197 4198 4798 2362 5815, 1961 '62; 4198
    - Jhap, 1961; 4798
    - Behar, 1957; 4987
    - Finn twins, 1961 Private Law 85-699; 5181
    - Martinezz, 1957 '58; 5514
    - Bonogarcia, 1957; 5515
    - Tai Ju So, 1961; 5815
    - Mae Bow Jung, 1961; 6228
    - Sallar Bill Tax levies HR451 4203 5737 6452 41 S 769, 1957; 6452
    - Saigu (Tuchi), 1961; 6458
    - Naonisa, 1961; 6515
    - Fontaica, 1957; 6928
    - Polorosa, 1961; 7611
    - Baldwin HR 10288, 1962 '60 '61; 8063
    - Fleming, 1961; 8064
    - Korosi, Sandor, Illona, 1957; 8146
    - Watanabe, 1961; 8173
    - Keh Public Law 87-301, 1962 '61; 8451
    - Sun HR 11911, 1961 '62; 8910
    - Shandler, 1962; 8932
    - Homeloans Guaranty Corp. (for against), 1958; 10637
    - Eng (ng) (Yook Gee), 1962; 10673
    - Kono (Toshinori), 1962; 10674
    - Taga (Mrs. Umeno), 1962; 10675
    - Apple, Daniels, James. (not Introduced), 1959 '58 '57; 10811
    - Jolan re-, 1962; 11246
    - Toon Ming Wong, 1962; 11285
    - Ron, Aharon, Maral, 1962; 11817
    - Yuk Wan Pam, 1962; 11893
    - Dokan, 1962; 11913
    - Singh, 1962; 13034
    - Niessal, 1962; 13074
    - Maltbuy claim bill, 1962; 13075
    - Loo Private Bill, 1962; Donald
    - Martin, 1957 '56; 1564
    - Hajnoczy/Csuka, 1961; 1567
    - Dordevioh HR 5736, 1961 '59 '62; 1568
    - Chan (bill withdrawn) HR 4500 6152, 1957 '55; 1568
    - Sakioka HR 6521[UNK] Private Law 87-229, 1961 '59; 1569
    - Chacon HR 6033 H J RES 307, 1957 '55; 1570
    - Huang HR 7168, 1961 '59 '62; 1570
    - Mino HR 4769, 1961 '59; 1571
    - Lotode HR 6193, 1957 '55; 1571
    - Yasuda HR 11996 Private Law 87-45, 1961 '60; 1572
    - Wartenberger (Bill withdrawn), 1957; 1572
    - Gallegos 60 HR 12353, 1961 '; 1573
    - Atcock HR 9222, 1960 '59; 1574
    - Shind HR 8058, 1957 '58; 1576
    - Weissner HR 10979, 1957 '56; 1581
    - Mendez HR 10981 H J Res 437, 1957 '56; 1583
    - Carcao (not re-introduced) HR 11101, 1957 '56; 1584
    - Mira Kovac 61 HR 9420, 1962 '60 '; 2362
    - Establishing inaugural date as legal holiday H J Res 448, 1957 '56 '55; H J Res 63
    - Repeal Ioth Amendment- Income Tax, 1957 '58; H J Res 256
    - Exception of Tariff for Trade Fairs H J Res 658 Public Law 85-402, 1958; H J Res 556
    - States rights legislation, 1958; H R 3
    - Oleson Danish award HR 11638, 1961 '60; H R 1345
  - 1957-'63
    - Permit Local Taxation cetain in process property for ultimate Federal Use, 1957, '55 '56; 745 (Box Box 14)
    - Repeal Admission Tax certain Benefited for Organizations, Religous H.R. 745 '61, 1961; 746
    - Extend Federal Air Pollution Control law, 1961; 747
    - Retired Military Personal Advancement in rank, 1961; 748
    - Mexican IndependanceMonument, 1961 '62; 1025
    - Foreign Service Academy, 1961, '59; 1026
    - Corrections Military Records, 1961; 1187
    - Equalize retired pay Armed Services, 1961, '60; 1188
    - Weather Reports to Airpolltion Control Agencies, 1961, '60; 1189 1297
    - Hospital Tax Excemption, 1961, '60; 2908
    - Ballot tempering, 1961; 3345
    - Motion Picture Tax Repeal, 1961; 3667
    - Commission in Federal Taxation, 1961; 3780
    - W.W. I Pension, 1961 '62; 4136
    - S.S. Earning Repeal, 1961, '62; 4683
    - Heading unclear, 5091
    - Ontlaw Communist Party, 1961, '62; 8043
    - Mass Transportation Fund, 1961, '62; 8332
    - Airpollution -- Auto, 1962; 9929
    - Tax Relief Small Business, 1962, '57; 9930
    - Gold Star Mothers S.S., 1957 '54; 9932
    - Military Contracts, 1962; 10251
    - Small Business Advisory Committee, 1962; 10805
    - Small Business Contracts, Maintenance, 1962; 10806
    - Health Insurance, 1962; 11194
    - Mass Transit, 1962; 11532
    - Japanese-American Tax Relief, 1962; 12819
- File of CASES
  - File of CASES, 1945/46 1955/56
    Arr. by Subject in manilla enveloppes folders
    - Agricultuere, 1945-'46 (Box Box CASES 16)
    - Civil Service, 1946
    - Civil Service, Jan-April 1946
    - Civil Service, May 1946
    - C P A, May 1946
    - Civilian Production Administration
    - C P A, Sept. 1946
    - Henderson Parker, 1945
    - International, 1945
    - Merchant Marine, 1945
    - Navy Dept., Jan-April 1946
    - Navy Dept. discharges, 1945-46
    - Navy Whitnall, 1946, '57
    - Special OPA Office of price adninistration, 1945-46
    - OPA, 1946
    - Orans, 1946
    - Railroad Retirement, 1946, '47
    - Tyler Kent, 1945
    - Veterans H RES 192 H R 536 2073, Jan-Juy 1945
    - Veterans, Aug.-Dec. 1945
    - Veterans, Jan.-April 1946
    - War Dept., December 1945
    - War Dept, H J RES 83 H RES 192, Jan-July 1945
    - War Dept., 1946
    - Federal Communications Commission, 1945
    - Office of Price Administration Inquiries (OPA), 1946, '45
    - Recommen-dations for position, 1946
    - Rivers Harbours H R 5434 7214 2033 4070 2711, 1945, '46
    - Tax, 1946, '45
    - U S Customhouse Federal office Building Public Law 519 836, 1956, '55
    - same arrangement, 1955/56
    - Patent Office, Jan- 1955
    - Post Office, Jan-June 1955
    - Navy Dept., July- 1955
    - Social Security Administration, Jan- 1956, '55
    - Veterans Administration, July- 1955
    - War Claims Commission, Jan- 1955
  - File of CASES, 1945/48
    Arranged by Subject. 80th Congress 1 2 Session
    Horizontal arr.: Subject, year(s)of introduction correspondance
    - Army, Jan-1948, '47 (Box Box CASES 17)
    - Civil Service, May-1947
    - Civil Service, Jan-1948
    - Civil Service, July 1948
    - Civilian Production Administration
    - C P A, May-1947
    - Favorable Action, 1947
    - Federal Housing Administration, 1947-48
    - F H A, July-1948, '50
    - Federal Parole, 1948
    - Federal Security Agency, 1948, '49
    - Gondol-Scott, 1947
    - Indian Affairs, 1948
    - Middlin Bonapart, 1947
    - Miscellancous, 1947 '48
    - Navy, May- 1947
    - Navy, July-1948
    - Navy, Augst -1947
    - Navy, Jan.-1948
    - O P A, May 1947
    - Patent, 1948-'49
    - Post Office Dept., Jult-1948
    - Railroad Retirement Board, 1947, '48 '50
    - State Department, Jan-1948
    - State Department, April-1948
    - State Department, July-1948
    - Social Security, 1947-'48 Agency
    - Supreme Court, 1945
    - Tax Refund, 1947
    - Treasury Dept., 1947-'48, '45 '46
    - U S Employee Compemsation Commission, 1947-50
    - Veterans, May- 1946
    - Veterans, Sept.-1946
    - War Department, Jan-1947, '46
    - War Department, May- 1947
  - File of CASES in manilla enveloppes folders
    Arr. aphabetically by subject
    1946/49
    Horizontal arr.: Subject, year(s) of introduction Corr.,related Bills
    - Army (Court martial cases), July-'48 (Box Box CASES 18)
    - Burea of interal revenue claims 80 Congr. I Session, 1949, '46 '47 '48
    - Case Bill letters 80 Congr. 2 Session PL 198 74 C folder against Case bill, HR 4908, 1947, '48 '46
    - Case Bill 80 Congress 2 Session, 1947, '48
      - Folder new Labor legisl.Case Bill HR 5262, 1946
      - (Labor) Case bill veto, 1946
      - Case bill legislative (Labor) HR 5262 4908, 1946
    - Civil Service, Jan 1947
    - Civil Srvice, Jan 1949, '48
    - Commerce Dept. HR 5470 PL 395, 1947-48, '45 '46 '47
    - Commerce Dept. (Embargo Diesel engine India), July 1948, '49
    - Interior Dept. S J Res 209, 1948, '47 '49 '50
    - Labor Dept., 1947-48, '46
    - Newsprint, 1948-49
    - Re-Contruction Finance Corp. (Greater China Town L A), 1948, '49 '50
    - Rent Control, 1947-48
    - Rent Control, July..1948, '49 '50
    - Request for personal recognition S 1415, 1946
    - R F C
    - Selective Service, Sept. 1948
    - Small Business, 1947, '50
    - Social Security, July -1948, '49 '50
    - Special Cases, July 1948, '47
    - State Dept., August.. 1947
    - State Dept. General, 1946, '45
    - State Dept., 1947, '46
    - State Dept., May 1947
    - Tariff, 1947-48, '46
    - Treasury Dept., 1947
    - Veterans, May 1947
    - Veterans, Augst 1947
    - Veterans, April 1948
    - Veterans Case Ford Sadie, 1947, '45
    - War Assets, April 1947
    - War Assets, May 1947
    - War Assets, July 1948, '49
    - War Claims Commission P L 896 75, 1949, '50
    - Public Health Service, 1947, '45 '48
    - Veterans, Jan 1948, '47
  - File of CASES aphabetially by Subject headers in folders, 1948/53
    - Civilian Defense, 1951-952 (Box Box CASES 19)
    - Commerce Department, 1951-1952
    - Commodity Credit, Jan. 1951-1952
    - Coast Guard Jan., 1951-1952
    - Defense Mobilization, 1951-1952
    - Displaced Persons, Jan. 1951-1952
    - Economic Cooperation, 1951-1952
    - Economic Stabilization, Jan. 1951
    - Economic Stabilization, Jan. 1951
    - Education Department, 1951-1952
    - Employee's Compensation Claim, Jan. 1951-1952
    - Export- Import, 1952
    - Federal Communication Commission, Jan. 1952
    - Federal Communication Commission, Jan. 1953
    - Federal Communication Commission, Jan. 1951-1952
    - Federal Communication Commission- California News Marketing, 1952
    - Federal Security Agency, 1951-1952
    - Federal Trade Commission, Jan. 1953
    - H.R. 841 Retirement with pay of Cdn. T. Gansa, 1948-1949
    - H.R. 1194 To amend Civil Service Act of 1954
    - H.R. 2560 To permit use of 20% National Service life insurace fund for purchase of Vet. loans
    - H.R. 7357 Relief of D.W. Kaisenberg
    - H.R. 8613 Relief of I.Rzmos- Romo
    - Judiciary Commission, Jan 1953
    - Justice Department, Jan. 1953
    - Korean Reconstruction, 1953
    - Labour Department, Jan. 1953
    - Los Angeles Housing, Jan. 1953
    - Maritime Commission (Merchant Marine), Jan. 1953
    - Mutual Security Administration, 1953
    - National Security Resources Board, Jan. 1951- 1952
    - National Production Authority, Jan. 1953
    - Political Lists
    - Personal Copy Government Affairs
    - Reconstruction Finance Corp., Jan 1951
    - State Department, 1949
    - State Department, 1952
    - Tariff Commission, 1951
    - Veterans, 1950
    - Vetarans, 1951
    - Truman' Marine Corps Lettes story, 1950
  - File of CASES arranged alphabetical by SUBJECT, 1948-1952
    - Airforce, Jan-1950? (Box Box CASES 20)
    - Army, 1948, '49
    - Army, July 1951
    - Army, 1952
    - Civil Service, Jan-1950
    - Federal building, 1950
    - Federal Communications Commission, 1950
    - Federal Communications Commission, 1951
    - Federal Housing Administration, Jan-1951
    - Federal Works Agency, 1949, '50
    - Justice Dept., 1952
    - L A HousingJan-, 1951, '52
    - Marine Corps, 1950
    - Navy Dept, Jan-1950
    - Navy Dept, 1952
    - Navy Dept, 1952, '51
    - Public Healthe Service, Jan-1951
    - Rail Road Strike, 1951
    - Recommendation for position, Jan 1951, 50
    - Social Security, Jan. 1952
    - State Dept., 1949, '48
    - State Dept., 1950
    - Veterans, Jan-1949
    - Veterans, 1950
  - File of CASES in manilla enveloppes folders, 1948/56
    Arranged by SUBJECT
    Horizontal arr.: subject, year(s) of correspondence
    - Airforce, Jan. 1957 (Box Box CASES 21)
    - Army (enveloppe), Jan. 1957
    - Cohen Marvin, 1950 '49
    - Indian Affairs, Jan. 1952 '53
    - Interior Dept. (enveloppe), 1954
    - National Security Resources Board, Jan. 1953
    - Navy Dept., July 1951
    - Navy Dept., July 1953
    - Navy Dept., April-June 1953
    - Office of Price Stabilization, Jan. 1953
    - Small Business Administration, 1953
    - Social Security Administration, 1953
    - State Department (enveloppe), 1952
    - State Department, Jan. 1953
    - State Department (Stein-Struck), 1948, '49
    - Treasury Dept., 1953
    - War Claims (enveloppe), 1958
    - Weather Dept. (enveloppe), 1956
  - File of CASES, 1949/52
    arranged alphabetical by subject headers in folders
    - Agriculture, 1950 (Box Box CASES 22)
    - Air Force, Jan. 1949
    - Air Force, 1950
    - Air Force, July 1952
    - Alien Property, July 1950
    - Army cases, Jan. 1950
    - Bureau Of Internal Revenue, Jan. 1950
    - Commerce Department, Jan. 1950
    - Census Case, 1949-1950
    - Census Case, 1951-1952
    - Census Data, 1950
    - Department of Interior, 1947
    - Displaced Persons, 1950
    - E.C.A., 1949
    - Federal Communications Commission, 1950
    - General Accounting Office, 1949-1950
    - Immigration Cases, 1947-1950
    - Immigration Cases, 1952
    - Indian Affairs, Jan. 1951-1952
    - Internal Revenue, Bureau of 1951-1952
    - Interior Department, Jan. 1952
    - Justice Department, 1949-1950
    - L.A. Eousing, 1948-1950
    - Loyalty case, 1949-1950
    - Maritime case, Jan. 1950
    - National Guard, 1950
    - National Security Resources Board, 1950
    - Navy Cases, Jan. 1949
    - Post Office, Jan. 1950
    - Post Office Department, July 1950
    - Post Office Department, Jan. 1952
    - Railroad Retirement, Jan. 1951-1952
    - Social Security, Jan. 1951-1952
    - Tariff, 1950
    - Veterans case Birmingham Hospital, 1950
    - Veterans Special Information, 1949
  - File of CASES, 1950/59
    Arranged alphabetically by subject in folders
    Horizonta arr: Subject, year(s) of corrapondance, related Bills
    - Airforce Dept. (douglas Aircraft Coop.), 1959, '58 (Box Box CASES 23)
    - Army, 1959, '51
    - Civil Service, 1952
    - Federal Social Security Benefits (F Heil), 1957 '55 '56
    - Fresco, Judth (Old Age Pension), 1959
    - Girard H J RES 61, 1957
    - Heaton H., 1957
    - Montes J C, 1954 '53
    - Moran, 1958 '60
    - Office of Price stabilization, Jan. 1952
    - Special Political H R 2780 S 795 2030, Jan 1951 '47
    - Tariff Commission, Jan. 1952
    - Treasuryy Dept., Jan. 1952
    - Un-employment Compemsation, 191 '52
    - United Nations, Jan 1952
    - U S Employees Compensation Commission (52, Jan. 1951
    - Veterans, July 1952 '53
    - Veterans (Colbert John W), 1959
    - Veterans 195 (public Law 86 633(, 1958 '54 '55 '56 '58 '61
    - Wage Stabilization Board, 1952
    - War Socialized Control, Jan 1951 '50 '52
    - RELIEF BILLS arr. by bill nr
      - Graves, 1957; H R 1567
      - Catherine Li H R 1580, 1957, '56 '59 '60; 1576
      - Miller H R575 8056, 1957 '56; 1578
      - Hamasaki H R 776 2955 8420 Private Law 870, 1957; 2295
      - MCCool, 1947 '48; 4487
      - Kassarjian, 1947 '48; 5423
    - Private Bills General, 1957 '58 '59
      HR 1566 1567 1568 1569 1572 1575 1581 1583 1582 2662 4357 3769 4987 8146 10981 11160 H R king Kay Kwong 1567
    - McDonough Bills Nr. range H R 115-7117 80th Congress I 2 Sessions, 1947 '47
    - A 5883 Constitunional Amendment to protect civil rights of U S citizens, 1951
    - Speech on H J Res 325, 1951
    - H R 5391 Wheather legislation, 1957 '58 '59
    - H CON RES 3 Freeddom of relions, speech Press H CON RES 47, 1947 '48 '45
    - Moran Case, 1958 '56 '60